Jester Hairston Collection MS040
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sound recordings related to Jester Hairston, 1940 -- 1990; 1960 -- 1980; MS040.001; 20.4 Linear Feet; 9 Digital Object(s)
  - A world of Christmas music, 1972; MS040.001.013.00005; The Sanctuary Choirs (Box 13)
  - Young peoples' forum '60, 1960; MS040.001.013.00006; Church of Christ, Porterville (Box 13)
    Hairston featured as artist./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./
  - [Prod] ARGOSY-4 [Scene] 2539-1, 2540-1, 2541-1 [This title is taken from notes on the record, there is no known original title], 1948; MS040.001.013.00007; Unknown (Box 13)
    Culver City, CA./ Metro-Goldwyn-Meyer Pictures./ 1 sound disc./ 12-inch./ Handwritten notations on record sleeve./ May be related to Hairston's work in the film industry./
  - BBB Cindy Sing (Fast) [and] It's Gonna Be- Full for Vocal [This title is taken from notes on the record, there is no known original title], 1950; MS040.001.013.00008; Unknown (Box 13)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Presto Recording Corporation./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ Handwritten notations on record sleeve./
  - Cavalcade of America [parts 1 and 4], 1952; MS040.001.013.00010; Unknown (Box 13)
    New York./ NBC./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Cavalcade of America [parts 2 and 5], 1952; MS040.001.013.00011; Unknown (Box 13)
  - Cavalcade of America [parts 3 and 6], 1952; MS040.001.013.00012; Unknown (Box 13)
  - [Illegible] County Chorus [illegible] by Jester Hairston, 1952; MS040.001.013.00013; Hairston, Jester (Box 13)
    [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Handwritten notations on record sleeve./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Duel in the Sun [Excerpts from the musical score of the David O. Selznick Technicolor production], 1946; MS040.001.013.00014; Tiomkin, Dimitri (Box 13)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 2 sound discs: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ May be related to Hairston's friendship with Dimitri Tiomkin and their work on the 1946 film 'Duel in the Sun'./
  - [Finian's] Rainbow [The Begat] [This title is taken from notes on the record, there is no known original title], 1968; MS040.001.013.00015; Unknown (Box 13)
    This date is approximate./ New York./ Audiodis [?]./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ Handwritten notations on record sleeve./ May be related to Hairston's work on the 1968 film 'Finian's Rainbow'./
  - Hollywood Sound Stage, Part 2, 1952; MS040.001.013.00016; Unknown (Box 13)
    Hollywood, CA./ Radio Recorders./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ May also include Part 1./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Hollywood Sound Stage, Part 3, 1952; MS040.001.013.00017; Unknown (Box 13)
    Hollywood, CA./ Radio Recorders./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ May also include Part 4./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Hollywood Sound Stage, Part 5 and 6, 1952; MS040.001.013.00018; Unknown (Box 13)
    Hollywood, CA./ Radio Recorders./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - It's gonna rain [and] Waltz / Zach & Father John, 1945; MS040.001.014.00001; Unknown (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [Presto Recording Corporation]./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./ The accompanying record sleeve has handwritten notations./ May be related to recordings MS040.001.014.00002 and 00004./
  - Negro Bon Bosh / Bon Bosh Pickup, 1945; MS040.001.014.00002; Unknown (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [Presto Recording Corporation]./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./ The accompanying record sleeve has handwritten notations./ May be related to recordings MS040.001.014.00001 and 00004./
  - Nobody knows the trouble I've seen, 1945; MS040.001.014.00003; Hall Johnson Choir (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ This may be related to Hairston's work with the Hall Johnson Choir early in his career./ The title is taken from the first song listed on a type written label on the record. There are nine additional songs listed./ The accompanying record jacket may not be original and may have been modified by Hairston to contain the record./
  - Plain BBB / Complete BBB Dance [Bon Bosh Boogie] [This title is taken from notes on the record, there is no known original title], 1945; MS040.001.014.00004; Unknown (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ [Presto Recording Corporation]./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./ The accompanying record sleeve has handwritten notations./ May be related to recordings MS040.001.014.00001 and 00002./
  - Virginia Music Camp Festival of Music [Shenandoah Chorus, side 1 and Orchestra, side 4], 1969; MS040.001.014.00005; Virginia Music Camp (Box 14)
    [United States]./ Century Records./ 1 sound disc: 33 rpm, 12-inch./ This may be related to Hairston based on his additional work with the Virginia Music Camp./ Original record jacket and accompanying material included./
  - Virginia Music Camp Festival of Music [Festival Chorus, side 2 and Massanetta Chorus, side 3], 1969; MS040.001.014.00006; Virginia Music Camp (Box 14)
  - [Untitled Record 001], 1950; MS040.001.014.00007; Unknown (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Century Records./ 1 sound disc: 33 rpm, 12-inch./ This may be related to Hairston based on his additional work with the Virginia Music Camp./ Original record jacket and accompanying material included./
  - [Untitled Record 002], 1950; MS040.001.014.00008; Unknown (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ 1 sound disc, 12-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content./ This record is badly degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be impossible./
  - [Untitled Record 003], 1950; MS040.001.014.00009; Unknown (Box 14)
  - Bright, bright star [record jacket only], 1960; MS040.001.014.00010; Hall Johnson and the Orphean Choir (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ Hollywood, CA./ Era Record Company./ 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket. It may or may not be related to Jester Hairston's work with Hall Johnson./
  - A Hairston Festival [record jacket only], 1973; MS040.001.014.00011; Roseburg High School (Box 14)
    Camden, NJ./ Recorded Publications Company./ 12-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./
  - Seasons [record jacket only], 1970; MS040.001.014.00012; The Jesters (Box 14)
    This date is approximate./ Kent, WA./ Woodmont Records./ 12-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston./
  - The sound of Jester Hairston: a concert of spirituals [record jacket only], 1962; MS040.001.014.00013; Hairston, Jester (Box 14)
    12-inch./ There is no record accompanying this record jacket./
  - Begin the beguine / Lover man, 1947; MS040.001.015.00001; Eddie Heywood and his Orchestra (Box 15)
    Includes label inscribed 'M. Hairston', possibly Marge Hairston./ This date is approximate./ New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Decca 23398 (78A)./
  - Earle Anderson, baritone, 1956; MS040.001.015.00002; Anderson, Earle (Box 15)
    Record jacket is inscribed with phone number of Johnny Lange./ Los Angeles, C.A./ Christian Faith Recordings./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket included./ Christian Faith Recordings cataloging number: EA-75./
  - I can dream, can't I? / The wedding of Lili Marlene, 1950; MS040.001.015.00003; The Andrews Sisters (Box 15)
    Includes label inscribed 'Hairston'./ This date is approximate./ New York./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Decca 24705 (78A)./
  - I was a fool to let you go / Bullfrog and the toad, 1940; MS040.001.015.00004; Deep River Boys (Box 15)
    Includes label inscribed 'Jester Hairston'./ This date is approximate./ New York./ Bluebird./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - A Jester Hairston choral festival, 1963; MS040.001.015.00005; Oregon State University (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as soloist and director./ Eugene, OR./ Century Custom Recording services./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - Lift every voice and sing, 1950; MS040.001.015.00006; Southwest Civic Chorus (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as conductor./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Pressed for the Los Angeles City Bureau of Music./
  - Lift every voice and sing, 1950; MS040.001.015.00007; Southwest Civic Chorus (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as conductor./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record sleeve included./ Pressed for the Los Angeles City Bureau of Music./
  - Marie / With love, 1950; MS040.001.015.00008; Simpkins, Arthur Lee (Box 15)
    Includes label inscribed 'M Hairston', possibly Marge Hairston./ This date is approximate./ Long Beach, CA./ Crystalette./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Mary's boy child / Venezuela, 1956; MS040.001.015.00009; Belafonte, Harry (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as artist./ [United States]./ RCA Victor./ 1 sound disc: 45 rpm, 7-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Victor 447-0323./
  - Mother Lode [Motherlode] choral festival, 1960; MS040.001.015.00010; Mother Lode Combined Choruses (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as director and artist./ Stockton, CA./ Quality Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ This record is degraded due to palmitic acid deposits and accessing any of the sound data may be difficult./
  - Mother Lode [Motherlode] choral festival, 1958; MS040.001.015.00011; Mother Lode Combined Choruses (Box 15)
  - Mule-work song, 1950; MS040.001.015.00012; Hairston, Jester; Hairston Sextet (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as artist./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Presto./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Pacific Music Clinic Chorus, 1955; MS040.001.015.00013 (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as artist and guest conductor./ This date is approximate./ Stockton, CA./ Quality Recording Service./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./
  - Ride, red, ride / So long, 1947; MS040.001.015.00014; The Charioteers (Box 15)
    Inscribed with the name 'Gertrude Johnson'./ This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Columbia./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Columbia 37399 (78A) or Columbia 37384./
  - Rosamunde, 1960; MS040.001.015.00015; Orchester der Stadtischen Oper, Berlin (Box 15)
    Inscribed to Jester Hairston./ This date is approximate./ Germany./ Telefunken./ 1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - Someone overhere loves someone over there / Hey, what you say, 1945; MS040.001.015.00016; The Four Tones (Box 15)
    Inscribed with the name 'Jester Hairston'./ This date is approximate./ [California, United States]./ Preview./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./
  - The Song of Easter [part 1 and 4], 1950; MS040.001.015.00017; Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians (Box 15)
    Record jacket inscribed by Fred Waring to Hairston./ [United States]./ Decca./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - The Song of Easter [part 2 and 3], 1950; MS040.001.015.00018; Fred Waring and his Pennsylvanians (Box 15)
  - Tarzan and the Mermaid, 1948-03-05; MS040.001.015.00019; Jester Hairston Choir (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as artist./ Los Angeles, CA./ Electro-Vox./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record sleeve included./ The title is typed on the record label. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Till my brother comes / Shoot you 4 more times, 1952-10-08; MS040.001.015.00020; Hairston, Jester (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as artist./ [United States]./ Alco Disc./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Original record sleeve included./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - United Nations Flag [cut 1 and 2], 1949-08-15; MS040.001.015.00021; Hairston, Jester (Box 15)
    Hairston featured as composer./ Hollywood, CA./ Electro-Vox./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ The title is typed on the record label. It appears to have been privately recorded
  - 1st side, 1955; MS040.001.016.00001; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ Los Angeles, CA./ Rainbo./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Epzile, 1955; MS040.001.016.00002; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Duo Disc./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ Original record sleeve included, with the notation 'Little Billy Boy, Hu=21133'./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Epzile good copy / Soon ep [?] will be done, 1955; MS040.001.016.00003; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Duo Disc./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - David / Waves, 1955; MS040.001.016.00004; Hall Johnson Choir (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ Paramus, NJ./ Presto./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ Notation on the record label ''David' by Dwight Strickland [and] Hall Johnson, sung by Buell Thomas[?]' verso: ''Waves' by Strcikland and Richard Ellsasser, sung by Buell Thomas'. May be related to Jester Hairston's work with the Hall Johnson Choir./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Eleanor Lewis, 1948-03-25; MS040.001.016.00005; Unknown (Box 16)
    New York./ Audiodisc./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Good will, 1950; MS040.001.016.00006; The Voices of Walter Schumann (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ Hollywood, CA./ Dub WRS Recording Lab./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - In that great gettin up morning, 1950; MS040.001.016.00007; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Notation on the record is ' D5700/ 78RPM/ Glace Mooce [?]/ In that great getting up morning/ choir and solo voice./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Lightnin', 1950; MS040.001.016.00008; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ New York./ Record Disc Corp./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Sextette, 1950; MS040.001.016.00009; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ Los Angeles, CA./ Crystal Tone./ 1 sound disc, 8-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. The title is taken from handwritten notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - Too close to heaven / I don't care what the world may do, 1950; MS040.001.016.00010; Professor Alex Bradford and The Bradford Specials (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Specialty SP 852 (78A)
  - Triumph Sports Cars, 1957-03-15; MS040.001.016.00011; Unknown (Box 16)
    Hollywood, CA./ Western Recorders./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Notation on record label ' 'Triumph Sports Cars' / Tracks A, B, C, D / KMPC / 10:45 Sat. Pre Check [?]'./ The title is taken from notations on the record. It appears to have been privately recorded./
  - [Untitled record 004], 1950; MS040.001.016.00012; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ National Hollywood./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content./ This record is degraded due to peeling shellac and accessing any of the sound data may be impossible./
  - [Untitled record 005], 1950; MS040.001.016.00013; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./Stockton, CA./ Quality Sound Service Recording./ 1 sound disc: 33.3rpm, 10-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content./
  - [Untitled record 006], 1950; MS040.001.016.00014; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Mirror Record Corp./ 1 sound disc: 7-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. Notation on the record label 'This Voice Letter was record at the USO-Club'. There is no information identifying its content./
  - [Untitled record 007], 1950; MS040.001.016.00015; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [S.I.]./ [S.I.]./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content./
  - [Untitled record 008], 1950; MS040.001.016.00016; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ National Hollywood./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content./
  - [Untitled record 009], 1950; MS040.001.016.00017; Unknown (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ New York./ Audiodisc./ 1 sound disc: 10-inch./ This record has only one track on side A and no tracks on side B./ This record may or may not be related to Jester Hairston. There is no information identifying its content. Notations on the record label were obliterated with pencil./
  - Who art thou? / No hiding place, 1950; MS040.001.016.00018; The Original Gospel Harmonettes (Box 16)
    This date is approximate./ [United States]./ Specialty./ 1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 10-inch./ Library of Congress shelf no. Specialty SP 861 (78A)./
  - Foreign language records related to Jester Hairston (12"), MS040.001.037 (Box 37)
- Sound recordings unrelated to Jester Hairston, 1910 -- 1989; 1920 -- 1950; MS040.002; 25.2 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains records owned by Jester Hairston, but not clearly related to him or his work. The records represent an array of musical genres from the 1910s through the 1980s.
  Most of the records from before the 1940s are rare, 10-inch, 78rpm recordings produced by some of the first American record labels. Included is the original inventory number of the recording label or the Library of Congress call number (when available). While we removed the 10-inch records housed in bound record albums, we preserved the original albums and cross-referenced them (early 10-inch, 78rpm records were generally sold without jackets). Some albums Hairston labeled with genre categories.
  Recordings dated after the 1950s are generally 12-inch shellac or vinyl records, which were relatively common and commercially available well into the 1990s. Foreign language records are located at the end of the series.
  This series is subdivided into four groups, and arranged alphabetically within each: 1. 12-inch records unrelated to Jester Hairston (roughly alphabetized) 2. 10-inch records unrelated to Jester Hairston 3. 12-inch foreign language records unrelated to Jester Hairston. 4. 10-inch foreign language records unrelated to Jester Hairston.
  - An Afro-American song book, 1984; MS040.002.017.00001; North Jersey Philharmonic Glee Club (Box 17)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - An Air Force panorama, 1972; MS040.002.017.00002; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
  - The Airmen of Note and Sarah Vaughn, 1984; MS040.002.017.00003; The Airmen of Note (Box 17)
  - America in motion, 1976; MS040.002.017.00004; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
  - America the beautiful, 1978; MS040.002.017.00005; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
  - Al Perry's favorite Hawaiian chants & hulas, 1956; MS040.002.017.00006; Al Perry and the Singing Surfriders (Box 17)
  - Alaska!, 1972; MS040.002.017.00007; The Ballard Chorale (Box 17)
  - All the songs from Walt Disney's Dumbo, 1959; MS040.002.017.00008; Churchill, Frank (Box 17)
  - Allan Hancock College a cappella choir, 1964; MS040.002.017.00009; Allan Hancock College A Cappella Choir (Box 17)
  - American art songs, 1965; MS040.002.017.00010; Andreassen, Alden (Box 17)
    1 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and sleeve included./
  - American celebration, 1979; MS040.002.017.00011; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
    2 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket included./
  - American celebration, 1979; MS040.002.017.00012; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
  - American vaude and variety, 1972; MS040.002.017.00013; Williams, Bert (Box 17)
    1 sound disc: 78 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - Amherst College Glee Club on tour, 1972; MS040.002.017.00014; Amherst College Glee Club (Box 17)
  - Anita Kerr's Christmas story, 1977; MS040.002.017.00015; Kerr, Anita (Box 17)
  - Anthology of music of Black Africa, 1969; MS040.002.017.00016; Senghor, Sonar (Box 17)
    3 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record box and descriptive booklet included./
  - Arise shine, 1967; MS040.002.017.00017; Independent School District No. 197 (Box 17)
  - The art of McHenry Boatwright: spirituals, 1968; MS040.002.017.00018; Boatwright, McHenry (Box 17)
  - Art Tatum, 1954; MS040.002.017.00019; Tatum, Art (Box 17)
  - Bach's greatest hits, 1963; MS040.002.017.00020; Swingle Singers (Box 17)
  - Best of '80 Marching Band, 1980; MS040.002.017.00021; Jenson Publications (Box 17)
    2 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ Original record jacket and descriptive booklet included./
  - Beethoven: Eroica symphony in E-Flat Major, 1964; MS040.002.017.00022; Rochester Orchestra (Box 17)
  - Bicentennial, 1976; MS040.002.017.00023; Singing Sergeants (Box 17)
  - A bicentennial celebration, 1975; MS040.002.017.00024; Goldman Band (Box 17)
  - Bicentennial Salute, 1975; MS040.002.017.00025; United States 33rd Army Band (Box 17)
  - Billie Holiday's Greatest Hits!, 1980; MS040.002.017.00026; Holiday, Billie (Box 17)
  - Black, brown and beige, 1952; MS040.002.017.00027; Ellington, Duke (Box 17)
  - Brand new song, 1976; MS040.002.017.00028; Frank, Fred (Box 17)
  - The Branko Krsmanovich Chorus of Yugoslavia at Carnegie Hall, 1963; MS040.002.017.00029; Branko Krsmanovich Chorus (Box 17)
  - The Branko Krsmanovic Chorus of Belgrade, 1963; MS040.002.017.00030; Branko Krsmanovich Chorus (Box 17)
  - 'Bubbles' (John W. that is...), 1964; MS040.002.017.00032; Bubbles, John W. (Box 17)
  - Buddy DeFranco and Oscar Peterson play George Gershwin, 1962; MS040.002.017.00033; DeFranco, Buddy (Box 17)
  - Calypso, 1956; MS040.002.017.00034; Belafonte, Harry (Box 17)
  - Calypso Christmas, 1956; MS040.002.017.00035; De Paur Chorus (Box 17)
    0 sound disc: 33.3 rpm, 12-inch./ There is no record jacket accompanying this record jacket./
  - Canciones de Espana, 1955; MS040.002.018.00001; St. Jordi Choir (Box 18)